A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Hugh Morrow Interviews, Series Q FA352
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Interviews with NAR Associates and Family Members, 1979-1980; 2; 4 Document Box(es)
  - Gene Spagnoli Interview, 1980 February 7; 37 Pages (Box 3, Folder 38)
    Reporter for the New York Daily News
  - Gene Spagnoli Interview, 1980 February 7 (Box 3, Folder 38a)
  - Phil Weinberg Interview, 1980 February 2; 33 Pages (Box 3, Folder 39)
    National Director of New York State Republican Committee
  - Phil Weinberg Interview, 1980 February 2 (Box 3, Folder 39a)
  - Flor Brennan Interview, 1980 March 6; 63 Pages (Box 3, Folder 40)
    Office of the Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs; Room 5600
  - Martha Dalrymple Interview, 1980; 20 Pages (Box 3, Folder 41)
    Office of the Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs; author of The AIA Story
  - Martha Dalrymple Interview, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 41a)
  - Carl Spad Interview, 1980 January 9; 21 Pages (Box 3, Folder 42)
    New York State Appointments Officer; State Chair of Young Republicans
  - Carl Spad Interview, 1980 January 9 (Box 3, Folder 42a)
  - James Cannon Interview, 1979 October 16; 48 Pages (Box 3, Folder 43)
    Gubernatorial and Vice Presidential Aide for Congressional matters
  - James Cannon Interview, 1979 October 16 (Box 3, Folder 43a)
  - William Pfeiffer Interview, 1980 April 5; 66 Pages (Box 3, Folder 44)
    Gubernatorial campaign manager for 1962 and 1966; State Republican chair.
  - William Pfeiffer Interview, 1980 April 5 (Box 3, Folder 44a)
  - Charles Metzner Interview, 1980 April 1; 28 Pages (Box 3, Folder 45)
    Gubernatorial campaign advisor for 1958; Judge
  - Charles Metzner Interview, 1980 April 1 (Box 3, Folder 45a)
  - Fiorvante (Fred) Perrotta Interview, 1980 March 11; 48 Pages (Box 3, Folder 46)
    Assistant counsel to the Governor, 1959-1960; NYC coordinator of the 1970 gubernatorial campaign
  - Fiorvante (Fred) Perrotta Interview, 1980 March 11 (Box 3, Folder 46a)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restriction-Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller
  - Edward Kresky Interview, 1979 August 24; 71 Pages (Box 3, Folder 47)
    Staff of Temporary State Commission on the Constitutional Convention, 1957; Deputy Chief of Staff to the Governor; Metropolitan Transportation Authority
  - Edward Kresky Interview, 1979 August 24 (Box 3, Folder 47a)
  - Steven C. Rockefeller Interview, 1980 June 27; revised 2005 March 2; 25 Pages (Box 4, Folder 48)
    Son. This transcript was edited by the interviewee in 2005 and opened with his permission in 2013.
  - Steven C. Rockefeller Interview, 1980 June 27; revised 2005 March 2 (Box 4, Folder 48a)
  - David Rockefeller Interview, 1980 July 10; revised 2014 March; 56 Pages (Box 4, Folder 49)
    Scope and Contents
    Brother. This transcript was edited for clarification by the interviewee and opened with his permission in 2014.
  - David Rockefeller Interview, 1980 July 10; revised 2014 March (Box 4, Folder 49a)
  - Sol Neil Corbin Interview, 1979 November 30; 67 Pages (Box 4, Folder 50)
    Counsel to the Governor; Assistant to the Governor in the Attica Riot investigation; Special Counsel to the Vice President for the Commission on CIA Activities
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller Interview, 1980 February 1 and March 15; 50 Pages (Box 4, Folder 51)
    Wife
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller Interview, 1980 February 1 and March 15 (Box 4, Folder 51a)